[
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0601_Watcher_Death",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0601_Watcher_Death_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0601_Watcher_Death_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0601_Watcher_Corruption",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0601_Watcher_Corruption_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0601_Watcher_Corruption_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0602_Magistrate_Windsward",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0602_Magistrate_Windsward_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0602_Magistrate_Windsward_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0622_Magistrate_Faction",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0602_Magistrate_Factions_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0602_Magistrate_Factions_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0602_Magistrate_FactionsReady",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0602_Magistrate_FactionsReady_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0602_Magistrate_Factions_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "S_factionchoiceready",
        "RequiredAchievement": "S_factiontalkedto",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0622_Innkeep_WhereNow",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0622_Innkeep_WhereNow_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0622_Innkeep_WhereNow_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0622_Innkeep_WhyHouse",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0622_Innkeep_WhyHouse_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0622_Innkeep_WhyHouse_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0603_Survivalist_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0603_Survivalist_01_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0603_Survivalist_01_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0602_Marauder_talk",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0602_Marauder_talk_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0602_Marauder_talk_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "S_introtomarauders",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0602_Syndicate_talk",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0602_Syndicate_talk_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0602_Syndicate_talk_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "S_introtosyndicate",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0602_Covenant_talk",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0602_Covenant_talk_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0602_Covenant_talk_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "S_introtocovenant",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0602_Marauder_dye_talk",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0602_Marauder_dye_talk_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0602_Marauder_dye_talk_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "S_marauderquest1",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0602_Syndicate_dye_talk",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0602_Syndicate_dye_talk_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0602_Syndicate_dye_talk_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "S_syndicatequest1",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0602_Covenant_dye_talk",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0602_Covenant_dye_talk_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0602_Covenant_dye_talk_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "S_covenantquest1",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "0623_Fisher_ExplainHotspots",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0223_Fisher_ExplainHotspots_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@0223_Fisher_ExplainHotspots_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    }
]
